[
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57]?",
      "correctAnswer": "54",
      "options": [
        "53",
        "54",
        "55",
        "56"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58]?",
      "correctAnswer": "55",
      "options": [
        "54",
        "55",
        "56",
        "57"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59]?",
      "correctAnswer": "56",
      "options": [
        "55",
        "56",
        "57",
        "58"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60]?",
      "correctAnswer": "57",
      "options": [
        "56",
        "57",
        "58",
        "59"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61]?",
      "correctAnswer": "58",
      "options": [
        "57",
        "58",
        "59",
        "60"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62]?",
      "correctAnswer": "59",
      "options": [
        "58",
        "59",
        "60",
        "61"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63]?",
      "correctAnswer": "60",
      "options": [
        "59",
        "60",
        "61",
        "62"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64]?",
      "correctAnswer": "61",
      "options": [
        "60",
        "61",
        "62",
        "63"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65]?",
      "correctAnswer": "62",
      "options": [
        "61",
        "62",
        "63",
        "64"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the median of these numbers:<br> [60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 160]?",
      "correctAnswer": "64",
      "options": [
        "63",
        "64",
        "65",
        "66"
      ]
    }
]